//create an array of objects that store the question, options and answers

const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Which US city is referred to as ‘Sin City’?',
      answers: [
        'New York',
        'Los Angeles',
        'Las Vegas',
        'Miami'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Las Vegas',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the capital city of Vietman?',
      answers: [
        'Quy Nihon',
        'Mumbai',
        'Tripoli',
        'Hanoi'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Hanoi',
       
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of Africa’s highest mountain?',
      answers: [
        'Mount Kenya',
        'Mount Elbrus',
        'Kilimanjaro',
        'Mont Blanc'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Kilimanjaro',
        
    },
    {
      question: 'What’s the capital of Venezuela?',
      answers: [
        'Caracas',
        'Lima',
        'Guayaquil',
        'Maracaibo'
        ],

      correctAnswer: 'Caracas',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'What time of the year is Mardi Gras in New Orleans?',
      answers: [
        'June',
        'December',
        'February',
        'August'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'February',
     
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the Mona Lisa found?',
      answers: [
        'National Gallery in Oslo',
        'Vatican Historical Museum',
        'Louve Museum in Paris',
        'Smithsonian in Washington DC'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Louve Museum in Paris',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'In which country is Punjabi - the world’s 10th most popular language -most spoken',
      answers: [
      'India',
      'Saudi Arabia',
      'Nigeria',
      'Papua New Guinea'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'India',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the ‘Forbidden City’?',
      answers: [
        'Beijing, China',
        'Algarve, Portugal',
        'Seoul, South Korea',
        'Bangkok, Thailand'
      ],
      correctAnswer:  'Beijing, China',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'The Galapagos Islands are part of which country?',
      answers: [
      'Fiji',
      'French Polynesia',
      'Tonga',
      'Ecuador'
      ],
      correctAnswer:  'Ecuador',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'Where’s the Burj Khalifa, the tallest building in the world?',
      answers: [
        'Shanghai',
        'Dubai',
        'Hong Kong',
        'Seoul'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dubai',
    
    }
];


